I've got two skills sitting in Claude
code. The real intake skill and the
seedings prompting skill. And before you
ask, you don't have to build any of this
yourself. Both skills are free and you
can find them in my Discord below.
Hopefully, they can do way more than
what I'm about to show you. They can run
this whole thing on autopilot, but I'm
doing it manually today because I want
you to see every single step. Claude
takes the reel apart and extract every
single frame. He make the full
transcript with the timing of every
single word. No gatekeeping. Both
skills, all the prompts, everything you
saw today is for free in my Discord. And
if this helped you, just drop a